Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Glide Foundation/Glide Methodist Memorial Church, 1964-1973
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Staff, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1966-1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 199, 4008, 4009.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: New life styles, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], July, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1240, 1241, 1297, 1298, 1301, 1302, 1304-1309, 1313-1315, 1317-1320, 1322, 1323, 1351, 1353-1355, 1357, 1359, 1360, 1363.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], March, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1682-1685, 1718-1725.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Celebration of Love, Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], October, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2329-2332.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Celebration of Love, Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, California [slides], 1972 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [slides], 1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Sammy Davis Jr., San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2696-2706.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Sammy Davis Jr., San Francisco, California [slides], 1971 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: For Youth, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], September, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2764-2770, 2792, 2793.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, California [contact sheets], January, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3269, 3270.
  - Glide Foundation: Lewis E. Durham, President [copy negatives and prints], 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Prints are numbered 3270.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Worship, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], March, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3295-3298.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Jesse Jackson, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3405, 3413, 3414, 3417.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Judy, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], December, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3574.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], August 26, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4007-4011, 4013.
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [prints], 1971 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Reverend Cecil Williams, San Francisco, California [copy negatives], 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California [slides], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church, San Francisco, California: Copies [slides], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Easter, San Francisco, California: Copies [slides], 1971 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Glide Memorial United Methodist Church: Images for Stanford Web, San Francisco, California: Copies [slides], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Reverend Don Kuhn 101-104 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Reverend Don Kuhn at the Erotic Art Museum, San Francisco, California [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Lemon 101-102 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Geo's [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Geo [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - George [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Smiley [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - LISA [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - UFW/Coachella [negatives], May 23, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Wedding [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Clarke, Joffrey A-D [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - January-September [negatives], 1960 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Fall [negatives], 1960 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - June [negatives], 1962 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Summer [negatives], 1962 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Fall [negatives], 1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - October [negatives], 1962 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - December [negatives], 1962 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - December/Christmas [negatives], 1962 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 1-33-63 [negatives], 1963 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - April-May [negatives], 1963 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - June-July [negatives], 1963 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - August-September [negatives], 1963 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - October-December [negatives], 1963 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - January-February [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - March [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - April [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - May [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - June [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - July [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - August-September [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - December [negatives], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - March [negatives], 1965 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - April [negatives], 1965 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - May [negatives], 1965 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - June [negatives], 1965 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - December [negatives], 1965 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Glide 101-105 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Glide 106-110 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Glide 111-115 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Glide 116-120 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Glide 121-125 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Glide 126-130 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Glide 131-135 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Glide 136-140 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Glide 141-145 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Glide 146-150 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Glide 151-155 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Glide 156-160 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Glide 161-165 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Glide 166-170 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Glide 171-175 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Glide 176-180 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Glide 181-185 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Glide 186-190 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Glide 191-195 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Glide 196-200 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Glide 201-205 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Glide 206-210 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Glide 211-215 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Glide 216-220 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Glide 221-225 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Glide 226-230 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Glide 231-235 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Glide 236-240 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Glide 241-245 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Glide 246-250 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Glide 251-255 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Glide 256-260 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Glide 261-265 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Glide 266-270 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Glide 271-275 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Glide 276-280 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Glide 281-285 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Glide 286-290 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Glide 291-295 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Glide 296-300 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Glide 301-305 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Glide 306-310 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Glide 311-315 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Glide 316-320 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Glide 321-325 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Glide 326-330 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Glide 331-335 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Glide 336-340 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Glide 341-345 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Glide 346-350 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Glide 351-355 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Glide 356-360 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Glide 361-365 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Glide 366-370 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Glide 371-375 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Glide 376-380 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Glide 381-386 [negatives], 1960-1973 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Series 4: Southern Christian Leadership Conference/Coretta Scott King, 1965-1973, 2006-2014
  Contains mostly photographic materials: contact sheets, prints, negatives and slides. Additionally there is a small amount of correspondence, newspaper clippings and notes. There are images related to the Southern Christian Leadership Conference in Series 2: Classics, Series 6: Black Star Agency, and Series 9: Computer Media/Digital Materials.
  In 1965 Bob Fitch went to Atlanta, Georgia to work as a photographer and photojournalist for the Southern Christian Leadership Conference from 1965 to 1967. He photographed Martin Luther King Jr., his aides and other leaders of the civil rights movement as well as the everyday people involved in the movement. After Martin Luther King Jr.'s assassination in 1968 Fitch photographed Coretta Scott King and her family during Martin Luther King Jr.’s funeral and during the Poor People’s Campaign in Washington, D.C. The series documents the Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear, voter registration and political candidates in the South following the passage of the Voter Rights Act, the Chicago anti-slum housing campaign, Summer Community Organizing and Political Education (SCOPE) Project, marches, demonstrations, People-to-People Tours, and the Poor People's Campaign. Some of the individuals photographed in this series include: Martin Luther King Jr., Coretta Scott King, Fred Shuttlesworth, Ralph Abernathy, Stokely Carmichael, Jesse Jackson, Andrew Young, James Bevel, Septima Clark, Dorothy Cotton, Annie DeVine, Harry Belafonte, Hosea Williams, Julian Bond, Mahalia Jackson, Sidney Poitier and Joan Baez.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identifications, 2007-2010 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identifications, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identification of 1966 Alabama voter registration and candidate campaigns, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identification of 1966 Alabama voter registration and candidate campaigns, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. photo identifications, 2007-2010 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. research materials, 1970-2000 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Notes and materials for Bob Fitch talk on Martin Luther King Jr., 1968-2016 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Field notes - Selma, April, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Bob Fitch's dates and chronology, 1968-2016 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identification project contacts, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Photo identifications and map of Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear, 2014 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Atlanta - miscellaneous [contact sheets], 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 104, 105, 182, 204, 220, 244, 348, 410, 412, 414, 416, 417, 455, 742, 752, 784, 857, 861, 863, 869, 881, 892, 896-898, 928.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCOPE staff at Freedom House, Atlanta, Georgia [contact sheets], 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 121, 172, 206, 390, 396, 411, 413, 437, 441, 442, 444, 446, 456, 551-558, 639, 703, 711, 758, 759, 761, 817, 916, 918.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCOPE campaign and Ku Klux Klan rally [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4311.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Georgia organizing [contact sheets], October, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 101-103, 107, 893.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Montgomery voter registration project [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 106, 108, 109, 111, 113-115, 146.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Atlanta [contact sheets], 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Southern Christian Leadership Conference's headquarters and dinner with staff and others, including Martin Luther King Jr., James Bevel, Robert Green, and Julian Bond, Atlanta, Georgia. Also includes image of Martin Luther King Jr. in his office in front of Mahatma Gandhi portrait.
    Contact sheets are numbered 112, 135, 171, 201, 209, 312, 342, 418, 425, 428, 448, 815, 865, 909, 911, 925, 968-970, 973.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Eutaw, Greene County, Alabama [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 116, 118, 119, 120, 122, 129-134, 136-141, 143, 148, 150-154, 168, 169.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. Alabama People-to-People Tour [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 161, 165, 167, 214.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. People-to-People Tour, Alabama [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 117, 123-126, 128, 156, 157, 160, 164, 170, 602.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Murder, Wilcox County, Alabama [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 202, 210.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Christmas, Birmingham, Alabama [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 173, 174, 177-181, 183, 184, 186-200, 203, 205, 207, 208, 213, 215, 217, 218, 220, 224, 226, 230, 232.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Christmas, Birmingham, Alabama [contact sheets], 1965 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 221, 225, 227-229, 231.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Chicago, Illinois [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    Martin Luther King Jr., Hosea Williams and other SCLC during the Chicago campaign with Dick Gregory and Jimmy Collier. Also includes images of Al Raby of the Coordinating Council of Community Organizations and the Freedom Festival with Sidney Poitier, Harry Belafonte and Mahalia Jackson.
    Contact sheets are numbered 238, 249, 250, 257, 261, 279, 281-283, 287, 289, 290, 298, 299, 303, 306, 308, 327, 328, 894, 917, 930, 931.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Singing, Chicago, Illinois [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    Jimmy Collier leading SCLC's Chicago campaign staff in song.
    Contact sheets are numbered 248, 256, 268, 270, 272, 275, 286, 288, 293, 315.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Chicago organizers - scoping out Al Raby, Chicago, Illinois [contact sheets], January, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Scopes and Contents
    Martin Luther King Jr., Hosea Williams, Andrew Young and other SCLC staff touring slums and meeting with residents during the Chicago campaign. Also includes images of Al Raby of the Coordinating Council of Community Organizations and the Freedom Festival with Sidney Poitier, Harry Belafonte and Mahalia Jackson.
    Contact sheets are numbered 251-253, 255, 258-260, 263-266, 269, 271, 273, 274, 276, 278, 280, 284, 285, 291, 292, 294-297, 300-302, 304, 305, 307, 309, 319, 329-333, 346.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Southern Christian Leadership Conference recruiting candidates to run for state, local and county offices, Alabama. Includes images of Walter J. Calhoun, Donnie V. Irby, James Robinson, James Perryman, Lonnie L. Brown, Albert Turner, William McKinley Branch Sr., Fred Gray, Martin Luther King Jr., H.O. Williams, Ralph Abernathy, Alberta Branch, Ann Braxton, David Hood, Lucious Amerson, Felix N. Nixon, Maggie Boreman, L.A. Locklair, T.Y. Rogers, Patt J. Davis, Walter J. Calhoun, Henry McCaskill and John Hewlett.
    Contact sheets are numbered 277, 310, 311, 313, 314, 316, 318, 323, 336, 339, 355, 363, 368, 370, 376, 379-382, 388, 389, 391, 392, 420, 426, 500, 501, 504, 506-525, 527, 528, 530-541, 543-546.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates: Thomas Gilmore for Greene County Sheriff [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 357, 373, 374, 377, 394, 460, 526.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates - Selma [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 317, 320-322, 324-326, 362, 369, 385-387, 445.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: King home [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 350, 351.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Black Belt [contact sheets], 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 352-354, 356, 358-361, 364-367, 371, 372, 375, 378, 384, 393.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr., Joan Baez and Harry Belafonte [contact sheets], October 15, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Harry Belafonte, Joan Baez, Sammy Davis Jr., and Martin Luther King Jr., during the Stars for Freedom tour benefitting the SCLC, Oakland-Alameda County Coliseum Arena.
    Contact sheets are numbered 372-377.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Atlanta conference/workshop for Alabama candidates, Atlanta, Georgia [contact sheets], April, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Training workshop for Alabama candidates for public offices, Atlanta, Georgia. Images include H.O. Williams, Martin Luther King Jr., Fred Gray, Ralph Abernathy, T.Y. Rogers, Albert Turner, Patt J. Davis and Henry McCaskill.
    Contact sheets are numbered 335, 337, 340, 341, 343, 344, 347, 349, 419, 431.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates - Martin Luther King Jr. tour [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 459, 469, 474, 495.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates - Martin Luther King Jr. tour [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 457, 461-464, 466-468, 470, 472, 473, 475, 477, 490.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama candidates - Montgomery conference, Montgomery, Alabama [contact sheets], May, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Scope and Contacts
    Contact sheets are numbered 338, 422, 423, 427, 429.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. tour - Brown Chapel, Selma, Alabama [contact sheets], May, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    Martin Luther King Jr, Fred Shuttlesworth, Andrew Young and James Orange speaking at Brown Chapel, Selma during a tour to promote candidates for Alabama public offices.
    Contact sheets are numbered 155, 158, 465, 471, 479, 496.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Martin Luther King Jr. Alabama tour - Kelly Ingram Park, Birmingham, Alabama [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Tour to promote and recruit political candidates for public office, including a rally at Kelley Ingram Park, Birmingham, Alabama. Includes images of Martin Luther King Jr., Martin Luther King III, Yolanda King, Fred Shuttlesworth, Hosea Williams and Bernard Lee.
    Contact sheets are numbered 458, 483-488, 491-494.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Alabama vote - Wilcox County [contact sheets], May, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 498, 499, 502, 503.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Day after election, Atlanta staff and others, Atlanta, Georgia [contact sheets], May, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 483-492.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear, Jackson, Mississippi [contact sheets], June 26, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear, with marching, rallies, meetings, setting up camp, serving food, locals reactions to the march, rally at Tougaloo College, entering Jackson and the final rally at the State Capitol. Includes Martin Luther King Jr, Floyd McKissick, Stokely Carmichael, Coretta Scott King, Ralph Abernathy, Juanity Abernathy, Claude Sterrett, Leon Hall, James Meredith, Andrew Young, James Brown, Marlon Brando, Burt Lancaster, Anthony Franciosa, Sammy Davis, Jr., Walter Reuther, and others.
    Contact sheets are numbered 560, 592, 623, 646, 649, 652, 654, 655, 658, 678-680, 682, 683, 685, 687-689, 702.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear [part 1 of 2] [contact sheets], June, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear marchers during the march, resting, setting up camp, and cooking food. Also includes Stokely Carmichael getting arrested and his later use of the "Black Power" slogan at a nighttime rally and white onlookers, journalists and police officers.
    Contact sheets are numbered 550, 559, 561-567, 569-571, 573-581, 586, 587, 589, 591, 593, 597, 598, 603, 606-610, 614, 616, 618, 621, 622, 624, 626, 627, 629, 630, 632-638.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear [part 2 of 2] [contact sheets], June, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear marchers during the march, resting, setting up camp, and cooking food. Also includes white onlookers, journalists police officers.
    Contact sheets are numbered 641-644, 648, 650, 659, 660, 662-664, 666, 668-677, 690, 691, 693-695, 697-700, 704, 705, 707, 709, 710, 714, 734, 737, 750.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr. [contact sheets], June, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear marchers during the march, resting, setting up camp, and cooking food. Also includes white onlookers, journalists police officers and El Fondren.
    Contact sheets are numbered 568, 582-585, 588, 590, 594-596, 599-601, 605, 611-613, 615, 617, 619, 620, 625, 628, 645, 647, 651, 653, 656, 657, 661, 665, 667, 692, 701, 706, 708.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Mississippi Meredith March Against Fear - Martin Luther King Jr. [prints], June, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Contact sheets are numbered 567, 583, 584, 604, 617, 620, 623, 627, 642, 643, 656, 697, 750.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Grenada, Mississippi [contact sheets], 1966 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Efforts to integrate schools, businesses and public facilities, with Martin Luther King Jr., Hosea Williams, Andrew Young and Joan Baez, Grenada, Mississippi.
    Contact sheets are numbered 718-730, 732, 735, 739, 747, 781, 785, 796-798, 800, 801, 803, 816, 825.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC convention, Jackson, Mississippi [contact sheets], August, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    SCLC 10th Annual Convention in Jackson, Mississippi. Images include Martin Luther King Jr., A.D. King, Fred Shuttlesworth, Ralph Abernathy and Andrew Young.
    Contact sheets are numbered 741, 743-746, 749, 752, 754, 755, 808, 895, 972.